shubham saad

WEB DEVELOPER

Profile

Web Developer experitse in **MERN** stack development with over 2 years of professional experience. Currently working as a React Js developer in the domain of e-commerce and finance. Seeking to apply my abilities in the world of IT for mutual growth and success

Employment History

Software developer, Waveaxis Pvt Ltd technologies, Bengaluru

UNE 2022 - JUNE 2023

- In this venture our first project is E-commerce web app UAE based product on MERN stack. I am start from scratch to convert the given prototypes into a responsive and full functional web pages with the help of "react Js, next JS, redux, tailwind css and media queries". I am also contributed on backend with the help of Node Js and Express Js. Additionally, design a fully functional admin portal, supplier portal and buyer portal to control the whole client side functionality like uploading the images of products, quantity, date etc.
- Proficient in utilizing Cypress for automated unit testing, demonstrating
 expertise in writing comprehensive test cases, executing end-to-end tests, and
 ensuring the quality and reliability of web applications by e
 e
 etively identifying
 and addressing bugs, regressions, and performance issues.
- Extensive hands-on experience developing scalable and efficient REST APIs using Node.js, leveraging its powerful libraries and frameworks to deliver
 eil cient and robust web applications
- · Working on relational and non-relational data bases.
- Experience in SDLC: Successfully executing the full software development life cycle, from requirements gathering to deployment, while ensuring e[®] cient collaboration and adherence to best practices.
- Proficient in utilizing Git for version control, demonstrating expertise in managing code repositories, branching, merging, resolving conflicts, and collaborating ell ectively within distributed teams, ensuring streamlined and ell cient software development workflo

Full Stack Developer, SocialTek, Hyderabad

AUGUST 2021 - MAY 2022

Successfully built and deployed feature-rich banking websites using React and Redux, leveraging their powerful component-based architecture and state management capabilities to deliver responsive, scalable, and highly interactive user interfaces, while ea ectively integrating with backend APIs and implementing secure payment gateways for seamless online transactions.

Freelance, Upwork

MARCH 2020 - JULY 2021

Working on small various small projects based on React Js and Tailwind Css.

Education

 $Bachelor\ of\ engineering\ in\ computer\ science, Indore\ Institute\ of\ science\ and\ technology, Indore$

AUGUST 2012 - JUNE 2016

Details

Indore India

9977047557

shubhamsaad777@gmail.com

Skills

ES6

Postgresql

Mongodb

React Native

Tailwind Css

Next Js

React Js

SKILLS

Only 2 pages have been converted. Please go to https://docs.zone and Sign Up to convert all pages.